Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- People (Container 184, Folder 21)
  Charney, Howard
- People (Container 184, Folder 22)
  Chari, Amalavoyal
- People (Container 184, Folder 23)
  Chaum, David
- People (Container 184, Folder 24)
  Childress, Tommy
- People (Container 184, Folder 25)
  Chiddix, Jim
- People (Container 184, Folder 26)
  Chu, Wesley
- People (Container 184, Folder 27)
  Cioffi, John
- People (Container 184, Folder 28)
  Cirigliano, John
- People (Container 184, Folder 29)
  Clark, David
- People (Container 184, Folder 30)
  Collbohn, Frank
- People (Container 184, Folder 32)
  Cortada, James
- People (Container 184, Folder 33)
  Crowell, William
- People (Container 184, Folder 34)
  Czapor, Edward
- People (Container 184, Folder 35)
  Day, John
- People (Container 184, Folder 36)
  Decker, Dwight
- People (Container 184, Folder 37)
  De Puy, Dave
- People (Container 184, Folder 38)
  Dewar, Jim
- People (Container 184, Folder 39)
  Diffie, Whitfield
- People (Container 184, Folder 40)
  DuBois, Paul
- People (Container 184, Folder 41)
  Dukes, Steve
- People (Container 184, Folder 42)
  Davidson, Frank
- People (Container 184, Folder 43)
  David, Ed
- People (Container 184, Folder 44)
  Davies, Michael
- People (Container 184, Folder 45)
  Doroit, Georges
- People (Container 184, Folder 46)
  Dreisbach, Timothy
- People (Container 184, Folder 47)
  Dumke, Mike
- People (Container 184, Folder 48)
  Dyce, Rolf
- People (Container 184, Folder 49)
  Dyson, George
- People (Container 184, Folder 50)
  Earnest, Les
- People (Container 184, Folder 51)
  Edelson, Steve
- People (Container 184, Folder 52)
  Eldridge, Frank
- People (Container 184, Folder 53)
  Elkus, Dick
- People (Container 184, Folder 54)
  Ellis, J. H.
- People (Container 184, Folder 55)
  Eshoo, Anna
- People (Container 184, Folder 56)
  Estrin, Debbie
- People (Container 184, Folder 57)
  Estrin, Gerald
- People (Container 184, Folder 58)
  Estrin, Judy
- People (Container 185, Folder 1)
  Faggin, Federico
- People (Container 185, Folder 2)
  Farber, David
- People (Container 185, Folder 3)
  Farmer, Jim
- People (Container 185, Folder 4)
  Fawaz, Marwah
- People (Container 185, Folder 5)
  Feher, Kamilo (Brown & Do)
- People (Container 185, Folder 6)
  Feigenbaum, Ed
- People (Container 185, Folder 7)
  Fellows, David
- People (Container 185, Folder 8)
  Fenner, Pete
- People (Container 185, Folder 9)
  Fenwick & West
- People (Container 185, Folder 10)
  Feshbach, Matt
- People (Container 185, Folder 11)
  Fisk, Bob
- People (Container 185, Folder 12)
  Flint, Ayame
- People (Container 185, Folder 13)
  Flint, Gary
- People (Container 185, Folder 14)
  Freeman, Peter
- People (Container 185, Folder 15)
  Flammer, George
- People (Container 185, Folder 16)
  Fletcher, Ann
- People (Container 185, Folder 17)
  Foster, Ron
- People (Container 185, Folder 18)
  Frank, Howard
- People (Container 185, Folder 19)
  Frei, Randy
- People (Container 185, Folder 20)
  Frezza, Bill
- People (Container 185, Folder 21)
  Friedman, Thomas
- People (Container 185, Folder 22)
  Friday, Robert
- People (Container 185, Folder 24)
  Gagnard, Jim
- People (Container 185, Folder 25)
  Gaines, R. Stockton
- People (Container 185, Folder 26)
  Gallagher, Bill
- People (Container 185, Folder 27)
  Galloway, Brett
- People (Container 185, Folder 28)
  Gaines, Stockton
- People (Container 185, Folder 29)
  Genensky, Samual
- People (Container 185, Folder 30)
  Geraghty, Dominic
- People (Container 185, Folder 31)
  Geske, Charles
- People (Container 185, Folder 32)
  Giannandrea, John
- People (Container 185, Folder 33)
  Gibbons, Jim
- People (Container 185, Folder 34)
  Gilder, George
- People (Container 185, Folder 35)
  Gillaspie, Norman
- People (Container 185, Folder 36)
  Green, Paul
- People (Container 185, Folder 37)
  Green, Jerry
- People (Container 185, Folder 38)
  Grey, Dick
- People (Container 185, Folder 39)
  Greenberger, Martin
- People (Container 185, Folder 40)
  Guss, Ray
- People (Container 185, Folder 41)
  Hafner, Katie
- People (Container 185, Folder 42)
  Hamilton-Piercy, Nicholas
- People (Container 185, Folder 43)
  Hanes, John
- People (Container 185, Folder 44)
  Hasenbank, Jim
- People (Container 185, Folder 45)
  Hass, Nelson
- People (Container 185, Folder 46)
  Hatfield, Dale
- People (Container 185, Folder 47)
  Hearst, Will
- People (Container 185, Folder 48)
  Hearst, Frank
- People (Container 185, Folder 49)
  Heilmeier, George
- People (Container 185, Folder 50)
  Henschel, Michael
- People (Container 185, Folder 51)
  Hingorani, Narain
- People (Container 185, Folder 52)
  Holzmann, G. (& Pehrson, B.)
- People (Container 185, Folder 53)
  Houser, Jan
- People (Container 185, Folder 54)
  Irwin, Manley
- People (Container 185, Folder 55)
  Jacobs, Irwin
- People (Container 185, Folder 56)
  Joel, Amos
- People (Container 185, Folder 57)
  Johnson, Johnny
- People (Container 186, Folder 1)
  Kahn, Bob
- People (Container 186, Folder 2)
  Kailath, Tom
- People (Container 186, Folder 3)
  Kao, Charles
- People (Container 186, Folder 4)
  Kavipurapu, Gautam
- People (Container 186, Folder 5)
  Keller, Michael
- People (Container 186, Folder 6)
  Kieburtz, Bruce
- People (Container 186, Folder 7)
  Kirby, Ken
- People (Container 186, Folder 8)
  Kleinrock, Len
- People (Container 186, Folder 9)
  Klitgaard. Robert
- People (Container 186, Folder 10)
  Koenig, Joe
- People (Container 186, Folder 11)
  Kramish, Arnold
- People (Container 186, Folder 12)
  Kramlich, Dick
- People (Container 186, Folder 13)
  Kuo, Franklin
- People (Container 186, Folder 14)
  Kwok, Timothy
- People (Container 186, Folder 16)
  Laitin, Howard
- People (Container 186, Folder 17)
  Larson, Joseph
- People (Container 186, Folder 18)
  Lasar, Matthew
- People (Container 186, Folder 19)
  Laubach, Mark
- People (Container 186, Folder 20)
  Lefman, Jonathan
- People (Container 186, Folder 21)
  Leghorn, Dick
- People (Container 186, Folder 22)
  Lemke, Jim
- People (Container 186, Folder 23)
  Lessig, Lawrence
- People (Container 186, Folder 24)
  Liebhold, Mike
- People (Container 186, Folder 25)
  Lin, Herb
- People (Container 186, Folder 26)
  Lipoff, Stuart
- People (Container 186, Folder 27)
  Lissauer, Saul
- People (Container 186, Folder 28)
  Loftesness, Scott
- People (Container 186, Folder 29)
  London, Jody
- People (Container 186, Folder 30)
  Lovins, Amory
- People (Container 186, Folder 31)
  Low, Kevin
- People (Container 186, Folder 32)
  Lucas, Jerry
- People (Container 186, Folder 33)
  Lukasik, Steve
- People (Container 186, Folder 34)
  Lustig, Herb
- People (Container 186, Folder 35)
  Lynch, Dan
- People (Container 186, Folder 36)
  Lyon, Matthew
- People (Container 186, Folder 37)
  Malone, David
- People (Container 186, Folder 38)
  Marggraff, Jim
- People (Container 186, Folder 39)
  Mascioli, Mario
- People (Container 186, Folder 40)
  Matthews. Robert
- People (Container 186, Folder 41)
  McDonald, Ed
- People (Container 186, Folder 42)
  McGraith, Ed
- People (Container 186, Folder 43)
  McMahan, Michael
- People (Container 186, Folder 44)
  McQuillan, John
- People (Container 186, Folder 45)
  McWilliams, James
- People (Container 186, Folder 46)
  Metcalfe, Bob
- People (Container 186, Folder 47)
  Merkle, Ralph
- People (Container 186, Folder 48)
  Meyerson, Martin
- People (Container 186, Folder 49)
  Millard, Linda
- People (Container 186, Folder 50)
  Millard, Steve
- People (Container 186, Folder 51)
  Mincher, Richard
- People (Container 186, Folder 52)
  Minow, Newton
- People (Container 186, Folder 53)
  Moley, Dick
- People (Container 186, Folder 54)
  Montagu, Anthony
- People (Container 186, Folder 55)
  Moretti, August
- People (Container 186, Folder 56)
  Morse, Samuel
- People (Container 186, Folder 57)
  Murthy, Kris
- People (Container 186, Folder 58)
  Myers, Gib
- People (Container 186, Folder 59)
  Napier, Joann
- People (Container 186, Folder 60)
  Nattiv, Moshe
- People (Container 186, Folder 62)
  Nichols, James
- People (Container 186, Folder 63)
  Nobuo, Ikeda
- People (Container 186, Folder 64)
  Noll, Michael
- People (Container 186, Folder 65)
  Norberg, Arthur
- People (Container 186, Folder 66)
  Nosbaum, LeRoy
- People (Container 186, Folder 67)
  Nycum, Susan (Buckley)
- People (Container 186, Folder 68)
  Odlyzko, Andrew
- People (Container 186, Folder 69)
  Omarr, Sydney
- People (Container 186, Folder 70)
  Omura, Jim
- People (Container 186, Folder 71)
  Onaral, Banu
- People (Container 186, Folder 72)
  Osterhold, James
- People (Container 186, Folder 73)
  Otellini, Paul
- People (Container 187, Folder 1)
  Panzaris, Yorgos
- People (Container 187, Folder 2)
  Papadakis, Constantine
- People (Container 187, Folder 3)
  Patterson, David
- People (Container 187, Folder 4)
  Paul, Sinil
- People (Container 187, Folder 5)
  Pelkey, James
- People (Container 187, Folder 6)
  Penzias, Arno
- People (Container 187, Folder 7)
  Perry, Mario
- People (Container 187, Folder 8)
  Perry, William
- People (Container 187, Folder 9)
  Personick, Stewart
- People (Container 187, Folder 10)
  Pettus. Michael
- People (Container 187, Folder 11)
  Pickins, Jeremy
- People (Container 187, Folder 12)
  Pickens, John
- People (Container 187, Folder 13)
  Pienum Publishing Corp.
- People (Container 187, Folder 14)
  Pickholtz, Andrew
- People (Container 187, Folder 15)
  Piel, Gerry
- People (Container 187, Folder 16)
  Porat, Marc
- People (Container 187, Folder 17)
  Postel, Jon
- People (Container 187, Folder 18)
  Pooley, Jim
- People (Container 187, Folder 19)
  Pouzin, Louis
- People (Container 187, Folder 20)
  Prodan, Rich
- People (Container 187, Folder 21)
  Pugh, Emerson
- People (Container 187, Folder 22)
  Rabinowitz, Mathew
- People (Container 187, Folder 23)
  Radow, Michael
- People (Container 187, Folder 24)
  Raissinia, Ali
- People (Container 187, Folder 25)
  Rao, Mohan
- People (Container 187, Folder 26)
  Rechtin, Eberhardt
- People (Container 187, Folder 27)
  Ricoh Company
- People (Container 187, Folder 28)
  Ritter, Mike
- People (Container 187, Folder 29)
  Roberts, Larry
- People (Container 187, Folder 30)
  Robertson, David
- People (Container 187, Folder 31)
  Robidarte & Associates
- People (Container 187, Folder 32)
  Roe, Arnold
- People (Container 187, Folder 33)
  Rogers, T. J.
- People (Container 187, Folder 34)
  Romiszewski, Peter
- People (Container 187, Folder 35)
  Rose, Christopher
- People (Container 187, Folder 36)
  Rosen, Charles
- People (Container 187, Folder 37)
  Rosenblatt, Syd
- People (Container 187, Folder 38)
  Rosenfeld, Leo
- People (Container 187, Folder 39)
  Rumsfeld, Don
- People (Container 187, Folder 41)
  Russell, Robert
- People (Container 187, Folder 42)
  Russell, Steve
- People (Container 187, Folder 43)
  Russell, Thelma
- People (Container 187, Folder 44)
  Sadr, Ramin
- People (Container 187, Folder 45)
  Saffo, Paul
- People (Container 187, Folder 46)
  Salwi, Dilip
- People (Container 187, Folder 47)
  Sandperl, Ira
- People (Container 187, Folder 48)
  Schleyer, William
- People (Container 187, Folder 49)
  Schneller, Chad
- People (Container 187, Folder 50)
  Schutte, Drew
- People (Container 187, Folder 51)
  Schweickart, Russell
- People (Container 187, Folder 53)
  Shapiro, Lee
- People (Container 187, Folder 54)
  Shattuck, Harold
- People (Container 187, Folder 55)
  Sheldon, Diane
- People (Container 187, Folder 56)
  Shobic, Martin
- People (Container 187, Folder 58)
  Siegal, Jack
- People (Container 187, Folder 59)
  Shubik, Martin
- People (Container 187, Folder 60)
  Simons, Jim
- People (Container 187, Folder 61)
  Sioshansi, Fereidoon
- People (Container 187, Folder 63)
  Sledge, Don
- People (Container 187, Folder 64)
  Smelick, Bob
- People (Container 187, Folder 65)
  Smith, Eric
- People (Container 187, Folder 66)
  Snyder, Jim
- People (Container 187, Folder 68)
  Solomon, Richard
- People (Container 187, Folder 69)
  Sonnenfeldt, Walter
- People (Container 187, Folder 70)
  Spilker, Jim
- People (Container 187, Folder 71)
  Spinrad, Bob
- People (Container 187, Folder 72)
  Spinrad, Paul
- People (Container 187, Folder 73)
  Spreng, Doug
- People (Container 187, Folder 74)
  Srikrishna, Devabhaktuni
- People (Container 187, Folder 75)
  Stacy, David
- People (Container 187, Folder 76)
  Stanniec, Tom
- People (Container 187, Folder 77)
  Steinbrecher, Don
- People (Container 187, Folder 78)
  Sterling, Bruce
- People (Container 187, Folder 79)
  Stewart, Bill
- People (Container 187, Folder 80)
  Swartz, Howard
- People (Container 187, Folder 81)
  Swensson, John
- People (Container 187, Folder 82)
  Snyder, David
- People (Container 189, Folder 1)
  Taleb, Belkacem
- People (Container 189, Folder 2)
  Targowslo, Andrew
- People (Container 189, Folder 3)
  Taylor, Bob
- People (Container 189, Folder 4)
  Taylor, Steve
- People (Container 189, Folder 5)
  Terry, Jack
- People (Container 189, Folder 6)
  Tesia, Nikola
- People (Container 189, Folder 7)
  Thompson, Archie
- People (Container 189, Folder 8)
  Thompson, Brian
- People (Container 189, Folder 9)
  Thomas, Jay
- People (Container 189, Folder 10)
  Thomson, James
- People (Container 189, Folder 11)
  Toffler, Al
- People (Container 189, Folder 12)
  Toole, John
- People (Container 189, Folder 13)
- People (Container 189, Folder 14)
  Truscott, Lorraine
- People (Container 189, Folder 15)
  Tucker, Karen
- People (Container 189, Folder 16)
  Twain, Mark (quotes)
- People (Container 189, Folder 17)
  Uesugi, Yasufumi
- People (Container 189, Folder 19)
  Uncapher, Keith
- People (Container 189, Folder 20)
  Utsumi, Takeshi
- People (Container 189, Folder 21)
  Vadez, Les
- People (Container 189, Folder 22)
  Vallee, Jacques
- People (Container 189, Folder 23)
  Vrij, Robert
- People (Container 189, Folder 24)
  Van Saun, R.
- People (Container 189, Folder 25)
  van Till, Jaap
- People (Container 189, Folder 26)
  Varian, Hal
- People (Container 189, Folder 27)
  Viterbi, Andrew
- People (Container 189, Folder 28)
  Washington, George
- People (Container 189, Folder 29)
  Waks, David
- People (Container 189, Folder 30)
  Wallgren, Anita
- People (Container 189, Folder 31)
  Ware, Willis
- People (Container 189, Folder 32)
  Warnock, John
- People (Container 189, Folder 33)
  Washington, Coleman
- People (Container 189, Folder 34)
  Weisner, Mark
- People (Container 189, Folder 36)
  Widrow, Bernie
- People (Container 189, Folder 37)
  Wheeler, Tom
- People (Container 189, Folder 38)
  Wilks, Ken
- People (Container 189, Folder 39)
  Wilks, Wyn
- People (Container 189, Folder 40)
  Williams, Tom
- People (Container 189, Folder 41)
  Wilmot, Robb
- People (Container 189, Folder 42)
  Wohlstetter, Albert
- People (Container 189, Folder 43)
  Wohlstetter, Roberta
- People (Container 189, Folder 44)
  Wohlstetter, Charles
- People (Container 189, Folder 45)
  Wright, Lori
- CableData (Container 191)
  ARTIFACT: Termcom unit & acoustic coupler model
- Marconi Date:920928 (Container 192, Folder 1)
  PB's Keynote Address for XVIII Annual Ceremony in Madrid, Spain
- Marconi Date:921015 (Container 192, Folder 2)
  Tentative agenda for 1993 Award in Lisbon
- Marconi Date:920506 (Container 192, Folder 3)
  Announcement of 18th Award Ceremonies to be held in Madrid, Sept. 29, 1992
- Marconi Date:930106 (Container 192, Folder 4)
  Announcement that Award will be presented to Dr. Izuo Hayashi
- Marconi Date:940408 (Container 192, Folder 5)
  Planning Session for 1995 Rome Symposium (memo from Gioia)
- Marconi Date:940427 (Container 192, Folder 6)
  Invitation for Bob Kahn's Award at the National Portrait Gallery, Washington
- Marconi Date:950707 (Container 192, Folder 7)
  Addison-Wesley acknowledges receiving "Is the UHF Frequency Shortage a Self Made Problem?"
- Marconi Date:950623 (Container 192, Folder 8)
  Bologna schedule, June 22, 1995
- Marconi Date:951117 (Container 192, Folder 10)
  Thank you note from Giola for Nov. dinner in PB's home
- Marconi Date:951103 (Container 192, Folder 11)
  Marconi Centennial Seminar, "One Hundred Years of Wireless", SRI in Menlo Park, Nov. 3, 1995
- Marconi Date:950805 (Container 192, Folder 12)
  PB's letter to Gioia expressing Fellows desire to assure the continuity of the Society
- Marconi Date:950001 (Container 192, Folder 13)
  3 books: "Marconi to the Music of the Universe," "Pontifical Academy of Sciences," "Civilta del Lavora"
- Marconi Date:950301 (Container 192, Folder 14)
  Historical Aspects of the Pontifical Academy of Sciences plus 2 other books
- Marconi Date:960717 (Container 192, Folder 15)
  Correspondence regarding a Symposium at Italian Academy where Fellows present their work
- Marconi Date:970701 (Container 192, Folder 16)
  Change of location for Marconi Society from polytechnic to Columbia Univ.
- Marconi Date:990506 (Container 192, Folder 17)
  Summary of Marconi international Fellowship Foundation (by Martin Meyerson)
- Marconi Date:990424 (Container 192, Folder 18)
  Photos from Bologna award Ceremony, April 1999
- Marconi Date:990201 (Container 192, Folder 20)
  Information from Meyerson regarding the Award Ceremonies in Bologna
- Marconi Date:990406 (Container 192, Folder 21)
  Phileas Fogg's travel information for PB to the UK and Italy
- CableData (Container 194)
  CableData presentations (in slide carousels)
- Com21 (Container 195)
  ARTIFACT: Com21 cable modem
- NAE, RAND, Winlab, etc. (Container 197)
  Misc. files
- IEEE Date:920401 (Container 198, Folder 1)
  Introduction to Ball Lightning by U.L. Prenn
- IEEE Date:950619 (Container 198, Folder 2)
  Invitation to attend 1995 Annual Stockholders Meeting of Macromedia
- IEEE Date:960924 (Container 198, Folder 3)
  Wire transfer of funds (from Paine Webber to Schwab)
- IEEE Date:990301 (Container 198, Folder 4)
  Magazine: IEEEPower Engineering Review, March 1999
- IEEE Date:000401 (Container 198, Folder 5)
  List, Board of Directors; Strategy for the Future
- IEEE Date:000120 (Container 198, Folder 6)
  PB - biography
- IEEE Date:000208 (Container 198, Folder 7)
  Lunch, March 2, with Cortada, Norberg, Keller, Saffo, and Herkovic
- IEEE Date:000218 (Container 198, Folder 8)
  Introductory letter from new President, Emerson Pugh
- IEEE Date:000228 (Container 198, Folder 9)
  Letter of Intent - PB's gift of $100,000 to History Center
- IEEE Date:000229 (Container 198, Folder 10)
  Discussion Draft: Supporting Information Technology History
- IEEE Date:000301 (Container 198, Folder 11)
  The IEEE Virtual Museum Strategic Plan
- IEEE Date:000302 (Container 198, Folder 12)
  PB memo to Uncapher regarding meeting with Norberg and others
- IEEE Date:000312 (Container 198, Folder 13)
  Understanding the Economics Underlying the Charitable Remainder Trust Concept by PB
- IEEE Date:000315 (Container 198, Folder 14)
  Paul Saffo - Essays
- IEEE Date:000401 (Container 198, Folder 15)
  The Life Members Newsletter, 2nd & 3rd Quarters, 2000
- IEEE Date:000409 (Container 198, Folder 16)
  Preliminary ideas to the proposed Foundation to Support the History of Computing
- IEEE Date:000409 (Container 198, Folder 17)
  Glaser - Article from Mercury News: "Institutions Creating Web knowledge Bank"
- IEEE Date:000901 (Container 198, Folder 18)
  IEEE Foundation Focus, Sept. 2000, Issue 1
- IEEE Date:001010 (Container 198, Folder 19)
  History of Computing Digital Library project between Hofstra Univ. and Virginia Tech
- IEEE Date:001101 (Container 198, Folder 20)
  Invitation to attend dinner with Emerson Pugh, Carlsbad
- IEEE Date:001101 (Container 198, Folder 21)
  Pugh's Carlsbad meeting presentation
- IEEE Date:001102 (Container 198, Folder 22)
  On Supporting the IEEE Foundation by PB
- IEEE Date:001001 (Container 198, Folder 23)
  IEEE Grid, October, 2000
- IEEE Date:000801 (Container 198, Folder 24)
  Newspaper: IEEE The Institute, Aug, 2000
- IEEE Date:001024 (Container 198, Folder 25)
  Letter from Andrews requesting contribution
- IEEE Date:010220 (Container 198, Folder 26)
  Letter thanking PB for gift of $3,000
- IEEE Date:010220 (Container 198, Folder 27)
  Information on deferred giving
- IEEE Date:010321 (Container 198, Folder 28)
  Thank you letter for support of Foundation General Fund
- IEEE Date:010516 (Container 198, Folder 29)
  Invitation to join the Goldsmith League
- IEEE Date:010901 (Container 198, Folder 30)
  IEEE Foundation Focus, Sept. 2001, Issue 3
- IEEE Date:011023 (Container 198, Folder 31)
  Invitation to join Pugh at the President's Gathering, San Francisco
- IEEE Date:020101 (Container 198, Folder 32)
  IEEE Foundation FOCUS, Jan. 2002
- IEEE Date:020303 (Container 198, Folder 33)
  Agenda for President's Gathering, March 3, Boston
- IEEE Date:020415 (Container 198, Folder 34)
  Request for a Bequest
- IEEE Date:020428 (Container 198, Folder 35)
  Agenda for History Committee, April 28, Newark
- IEEE Date:020429 (Container 198, Folder 36)
  Agenda for Trustees, History Center, April 29, Newark (and backup materials)
- IEEE Date:030225 (Container 198, Folder 37)
  Thank you letter for $20,000 for Solomon Restoration Project
- IEEE Date:030701 (Container 198, Folder 38)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, July, 2003
- IEEE Date:030901 (Container 198, Folder 39)
  Update on History Center and request for support
- IEEE Date:030929 (Container 198, Folder 40)
  Agenda for History Committee, Sept. 29, Baltimore
- IEEE Date:030929 (Container 198, Folder 41)
  Minutes of the History Committee and Trustees of History Center
- IEEE Date:031008 (Container 198, Folder 42)
  Minutes of the Archives Symposium held by the IEEE History Center
- IEEE Date:031029 (Container 198, Folder 43)
  2004 Membership Invoice (VISA card for $88)
- IEEE Date:031122 (Container 198, Folder 44)
  2003 Personal Planning Guide
- IEEE Date:040101 (Container 198, Folder 45)
  IEEE Life Members Newsletter
- IEEE Date:040104 (Container 198, Folder 46)
  Agenda: joint meeting of IEEE History Committee & Trustees, Nov. 14, Newark
- IEEE Date:040301 (Container 198, Folder 47)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, March 2004
- IEEE Date:040507 (Container 198, Folder 48)
  Invitation from Jerome Suran to join Goldsmith League
- IEEE Date:040513 (Container 198, Folder 49)
  Request to contribute to IEEE "The Spectrum" (PB turned it down)
- IEEE Date:040617 (Container 198, Folder 50)
  Draft of minutes from teleconference of June 2
- IEEE Date:040827 (Container 198, Folder 51)
  Announcement of joint fall meeting of IEEE History Committee and the Trustees of His. Center
- IEEE Date:040901 (Container 198, Folder 52)
- IEEE Date:041001 (Container 198, Folder 53)
  Newsletter: IEEE Life Members, 4th and 1st quarters, 2004-05
- IEEE Date:050301 (Container 198, Folder 54)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, March 2005
- IEEE Date:050427 (Container 198, Folder 55)
  Agenda and attachments for the History Committee and Trustees of History Center, May 8, 2005
- IEEE Date:050508 (Container 198, Folder 56)
  Minutes of the History Committee and Trustees of History Center, May 8, 2005
- IEEE Date:050701 (Container 198, Folder 57)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, July 2005
- IEEE Date:051208 (Container 198, Folder 58)
  Agenda and attachments for Trustee teleconference, Dec. 12, 2005
- IEEE Date:060301 (Container 198, Folder 59)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, March 2006
- IEEE Date:061101 (Container 198, Folder 60)
  Newsletter: IEEE History Center, Nov. 2006
- IEEE Date:061113 (Container 198, Folder 61)
  Thanks from Michael Geselowitz for PB's support
- IEEE Date:061201 (Container 198, Folder 62)
  Newsletter: IEEE Life Members, Dec. 2006
- IEEE Date:061205 (Container 198, Folder 63)
  Material for Trustees teleconference, Dec. 12, 2006
- IEEE Date:061201 (Container 198, Folder 64)
- IEEE Date:061207 (Container 198, Folder 65)